[Music]
Justin age 30 single is currently
working as an internal auditor he lives
with his elderly mother who is a
retire what if critical illness strikes
and Justin must stop working temporarily
what could happen without an income
Justin and his mother will face
Financial burdens such as daily living
expenses his mother's medical expenses
other expenses incurred due to Justin's
illness how can Justin protect himself
and his family
Justin purchased a manual life critical
illness insurance plan with a sum
insured of
$100,000 to enhance his coverage he
chose an option which allowed him to
make multiple critical illness claims at
the age of 40 Justin was diagnosed with
early stage cancer receiving a one-time
payout of
$100,000 2 years later his condition
deteriorated to an advanced stage cancer
he received a second payout 2 years
later he was diagnosed with another
critical illness and he received a third
payout in total he received three
payouts from his critical illness
insurance plan these payouts helped to
ease his financial burden while he
focused on getting the necessary
treatments speak to our Financial
Consultant and get protected with manual
life today